Sabir Süleymanlı

suleymanli.sabir@anticverse.com

linkedin.com/in/sabirs/

github.com/sabir-suleyman

About

I am a soph student of Computer Engineering at Uludağ University. With the knowledge I have, I want to not only stay at this level, but also contribute to developing technologies and make new inventions in the long term. My goal is to learn and to experience new things is to improve and do my best. I have a great interest in web technologies and I try developing myself more and more in this field. In addition, I am trying to advance in the fields of artificial intelligence and cyber security.

Education

BURSA ULUDAG UNIVERSITY

Bachelor of Science, 3.21 as of December 2022

Bursa, Türkiye Sept. 2021 - Present

Experience

TECHNOLOGY AND PHILOSOPHY COMMUNITY

Leader April 2023 - Present

ANTICVERSE WEBRAIDER

Vice Ecol Leader | Board Member Dec. 2022 - Present

GOOGLE DEVELOPER STUDENT CLUBS ULUDAG

Co-Leader of Project dep. Sept. 2022 - March 2023

ULUDAG SOFTWARE COMMUNITY

Co-Leader of Project dep. Sept. 2022 - March 2023

IEEE STUDENT BRANCH ULUDAG

Clerk of RAS (Robotics & Automation Society) Jan. 2022 - July 2022

GMT DORA IHA TEKNOFEST TEAM

Software Manager of the team Nov. 2021 - August 2022

Certificates

GLOBAL AI HUB

- Akbank Python Bootcamp

 Leading the team building pizza sales automation(PyPizza)
- Aygaz AI Literacy Bootcamp
- The First Step to Artificial Intelligence
- Introduction to Python



Skills

Hard Skills:

C,intermediate, C#,intermediate,

Python,intermediate, HTML,advanced,

Javascript,beginner, Git,intermediate,

Sass/SCSS,beginner, Linux,intermediate,

Networking,beginner.

Soft Skills:

Project Management, Time Management, Leadership, Google DSC Uludag, Software Community and Technology and Philosophy Community.

Languages:

Azerbaijani, native or bilingual proficiency, Turkish, native or bilingual proficiency, English, professional working proficiency.

Projects

"DORA" Unmanned Aerial Vehicle

Teknofest 2022 quadcopter type UAV designed to compete in the Rotary Wing UAV category and fulfill the given tasks.

ANTİCKET

A ticket trading platform developed for Teknofest 2023, using NFT technology.